{
    "questions":[
        {
            "index": 0,
            "question": "Red Hair?",
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "Green Hair?",
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "Brown Hair?",
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "Blond Hair?",
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "Tatoos?",
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Red tshirt?",
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "Green tshirt?",
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "Blue Tshirt?",
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "Glasses?",
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "Backpack?",
            "answer": 3
        }
    ]
}